http://www.dairylandinsurance.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Welcome to DairylandInsurance.com and myqual.dairylandinsurance.com which are owned and operated by Sentry Insurance a Mutual Company and/or its subsidiary and affiliated companies (collectively, “Sentry”). Sentry respects the privacy of each user who visits our websites. Sentry has adopted this website Privacy Policy ("Policy") to memorialize Sentry's current data collection and disclosure policies and practices for DairylandInsurance.com,  my.dairylandinsurance.com, and all related pages, mobile applications, information, databases, materials and services (collectively, the “Site”),. Dairyland ® brand property and casualty coverages are underwritten by a member of the Sentry Insurance Group, Stevens Point, WI. Unless otherwise specified herein, the term “Sentry” shall apply to the brand and underwriting companies. For a complete listing of Dairyland ® brand underwriting companies and state licenses Click Here.
Description of information practices
Remarketing and Third Party Use
Consent
Children
Collection of information
Links to other sites
Disclosure of information
Use of information
Description of information practices
To make fair insurance decisions, we must gather accurate information. Your insurance application and data you provide on the Site are our primary source of information. In some cases we may receive information from a consumer reporting agency that indicates your credit worthiness and credit history, as well as information regarding your driving record and claim history.   The information contained in a report prepared for us by an outside agency may be kept by the agency and disclosed to others.
We will not release information about you to other persons or organizations without your authorization except in these instances: (1) to our employees, agents or affiliated companies only when necessary in the handling of your insurance; (2) to insurance support organizations established to control insurance crimes or fraud; (3) to organizations not affiliated with us when necessary to complete your insurance transactions; and (4) if we are required or permitted to do so by statute, regulation, subpoena, a court of law or law enforcement authorities.
If you feel we have inaccurate information about you, you may ask that it be corrected, amended or deleted. Please send your request in writing with proper identification to the above address. We'll notify you of any action taken, or that we are unable to comply with your request. In that case, you can place a concise statement of what you believe to be correct information in our records. Your statement will be included in any subsequent disclosure of recorded information.
If we decline an application for coverage or cancel a policy, we'll give the specific reasons for the decision to the Named Insured. If our decision was based on an outside agency's report, we'll provide the agency's name and address.
Remarketing and Third Party Use
The Site uses Display Advertising. Display Advertising includes features such as remarketing, interest category advertising, similar audience advertising, and other types of interest-based advertising. Third-party vendors, including Google, show DairylandInsurance.com ads on sites across the Internet.
The Site and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the Double-click cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on past visits to our website. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager.
Consent
By using the Site, you consent to this privacy policy. If you do not consent to this privacy policy, please refrain from use of the Site. All information gathered from the Site will be stored and processed in the United States. If you access the Site from a location other than the United States, your use of the Site constitutes consent to the transfer of your information to the United States.
Children
The Site is not intended for children. Sentry does not knowingly or specifically collect personal information from persons under 13 years of age. In the event that Sentry becomes aware that we have collected personal information from a person under 13 years of age, we will delete such information from our database. Sentry does not authorize persons less than 13 years of age to use the Site or Sentry products or services.
Collection of information
Sentry may collect personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, Social Security Number, driver's license number and credit card or bank information for online payments or purchases) from users at certain locations on the Site. Sentry also collects non-personal and anonymous information from users to be used in an aggregate fashion. For example, Sentry may collect system-related information, such as an IP address, browser type and operating system type to be used for system administration purposes, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to monitor traffic patterns, to determine which services are used most frequently and to assess site usage. Sentry may retain information we gather about you indefinitely.
Links to other sites
The Site may contain links to other websites. Sentry is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of websites not owned by Sentry that may link to or may be linked from the Site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms and conditions of such websites so that you understand how those companies collect, use and share your information.
Disclosure of information
Sentry may disclose personally identifiable and aggregate anonymous information (information that is not personally identifiable) to companies and individuals hired to perform functions on our behalf. These companies and individuals may have access to your personal information to perform their functions.
Sentry may also disclose personally identifiable information to regulatory and credit agencies as deemed appropriate by Sentry for the purpose of providing services. For example, Sentry may disclose personally identifiable information to a regulatory or credit agency to obtain credit or motor vehicle report(s).
If one of Sentry's business lines or the entire business, or a substantial portion thereof, is acquired or transferred, whether by merger, consolidation or purchase of a substantial portion of assets, Sentry may disclose and transfer your personally identifiable information to such third party acquiring Sentry. In addition, if Sentry becomes the subject of a bankruptcy or insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, Sentry or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, assign, license or otherwise transfer such information in a transaction approved by the appropriate court. Sentry may also disclose your personal information to third parties when we believe, in good faith and in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) enforce or apply the Terms and Conditions of the Site; (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements; (c) protect the rights, property or safety of Sentry, our users or other third parties; or (d) prevent a crime or protect national security.
Sentry may disclose aggregate anonymous information to its clients, business partners, merchants, advertisers, potential advertisers, investors, potential buyers and other third parties if Sentry deems such disclosure, in its sole discretion, to have sound business reasons or justification.
When you access the Site through any co-branded websites or linked web pages, your personal information may be disclosed to and become the property of both Sentry and the relevant co-sponsor. In that case, the use of your personally identifiable information by the co-sponsor company will be subject to the privacy policy of that company, and Sentry is not responsible for nor subject to the co-sponsor's policy regarding their use of your personally identifiable information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and practices of any relevant co-sponsor before supplying any personal information.
Use of information
Information gathered is used to operate and improve the Site and Sentry's services, to create a positive user experience, and to deliver information on various products and services we offer. We may also use information we gather to inform you of new products or services available or under consideration, technical issues, customer satisfaction surveys or account updates and related purposes.
If you desire to purchase an insurance policy from the Site, Sentry may require you to provide your driver's license number and/or Social Security Number for the purposes of verifying your identity in a commercially reasonable manner and setting the premiums associated with purchasing such a policy.
How to review and correct information collected
If you have questions about information we may have about you, we will release details on the nature of information held in our records. Information contained in a report prepared by a reporting agency will be disclosed only through that agency. To get this information contact: Sentry Insurance, Office of Consumer Affairs, 1800 North Point Drive, Stevens Point, Wisconsin 54481. We'll then send our inquiry form for you to complete and return to us.
Cookies
Sentry uses "cookies" for the convenience of our users and to enhance your experience using the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is recorded either temporarily or persistently on your hard drive by a Web page server and is not used to deliver viruses or other harmful programs to your computer. By relying on cookies, Sentry is able to deliver a more efficient service that is more personalized for each user. Additionally, cookies allow Sentry to monitor traffic patterns, Site usage, and session information, such as items that you add to a shopping cart, which help make the Site more useful.
Why we require your e-mail address
Your e-mail address serves two purposes. It provides a username for retrieving saved information, along with a password you choose. It is also an avenue of communication for important information regarding your application and policy. You will receive information from us regarding your online transactions. You may also receive marketing communication from us. These e-mail pieces will contain a link to opt-out of marketing communication should you choose.
Security
Sentry uses industry standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving data exchanged through the Site. We also have security measures in place at our physical facilities to help protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at the Site. Although we have implemented various measures to help protect your information, Sentry does not guarantee the security of any information.
Privacy Policy changes
Sentry reserves the right to change the Policy at any time. In particular, Sentry may modify the Policy to reflect changes in the way we collect, use or disclose information or to reflect changes in privacy laws, regulations and/or industry standards. We encourage you to review the Policy when accessing the Site. Continued use of the Site following changes indicates your acceptance of the changes.
Applicable law
The Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of Wisconsin, without regard to conflicts of law principles, and exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any dispute arising out of the Policy shall be the state courts or district federal courts of Wisconsin.
California privacy policy
View the California privacy policy.
Contact information
If you have questions regarding the Privacy Policy please contact us at:
Julia Fullerton, JD, CIPP/US, CIPP/E
Director of Privacy
Sentry Insurance
1800 North Point Drive
Stevens Point, WI 54481
Phone 715-346-7271
E-mail: Julia.fullerton@sentry.com
Retrieve Your Quote
By personal info
By quote number
Fill in the fields below to help us find your quote.
Quote Number: *
Last Name: *
Email Address: *
Date of Birth: *
ZIP code: *
* required field
Please wait while we locate some quotes for you...
Whoa, something has gone terribly wrong when searching for quotes!
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Please try again later, or call our customer support number: 800-334-0090.
is invalid, please correct
is required
Cancel
Submit
×
No Quotes Found
We’re sorry. The info provided does not match our records. Please verify and try again. The quotes you are searching for may also be associated with an account. You also can retrieve a quote by Email, quote number or start a new quote.
Close
Try Again
×
Your Saved Quotes
Below is a list of quotes you started, so you can pick up where you left off!  If you have questions, please contact one of our sales professionals at 866-324-7952.
Quoted On
Vehicle
Continue Quote
Don't see your quote?  Search by quote number
Close
Start Your Quote
Get a price, get covered, and get on your way.
ZIP code *
Product Offerings
Motorcycle
Auto
is invalid, please correct
is required
Cancel
Get a Quote
Call for a quote
Monday - Friday: 7 a.m. - 9 p.m. CST
Saturday; 8 a.m. - 6 p.m. CST
Call 888-344-4357
At this time, Dairyland Insurance does not quote insurance online in [STATE].  Call us to get a competitive quote.
CallPartner
Call Partner
We're sorry
At this time, Dairyland Insurance does not write policies in [STATE].  Please check back next time your're looking to purchase a policy.  We're constantly weighing options to expand our service area.
Visit our friend
At this time, Dairyland Insurance does not write [PRODUCT] policies in [STATE].  We can, however, refer you to our preferred vendor – Answer Financial – who can help you compare prices and make your purchase.
Call Answer Financial at 800-761-6111
Get an online quote at answerfinancial.com
Visit our friend
At this time, Dairyland Insurance does not write [PRODUCT] policies in [STATE].  We can, however, refer you to our preferred vendor – Insurance Technology Corp. – who can help you compare prices and make your purchase.
Call ITC at 800-383-3482
Get an online quote at getitc.com
Visit our friend
At this time, Dairyland Insurance does not write [PRODUCT] policies in [STATE].  We can, however, refer you to our preferred vendor – INSURAMATCH – who can help you compare prices and make your purchase.
Call INSURAMATCH at
888-971-0155
Get an online quote at INSURAMATCH
Close
Find an agent
To find an authorized representative near you, please provide the following information:
Please wait while we locate some agents for you...
Perform a search above
No agents were found who match your search.
To get help finding an agent, call us 800-334-0090
Building Google map, please be patient while we place the marker points...
results found.
Whoa, something has gone terribly wrong when searching for agents!
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Please try again later, or call our customer support number: 800-334-0094.
Close
Unsupported Browser
Warning, we have detected that you are running an unsupported browser.
We recommend upgrading your browser or running on a different browser.
In the meantime, this site may not operate completely.
Close
